Guide to the Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh, J. Dennis O'Connor, Administrative Files, 1991-1995 UA.2.10.1991-1995
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Mail Log Files, 1991-1995; I.
  - Colleges and Universities, 13.
    - Penn State University, 13.4.
      - 13.4. Penn State University, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 38)
      - 13.4. Penn State University, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - Robert Morris College, 13.5.
      - 13.5. Robert Morris College, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 40)
    - Temple University, 13.6.
      - 13.6. Temple University, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 41)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 13.7.
      - 13.7. University of Pennsylvania, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 42)
      - 13.7. University of Pennsylvania, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 43)
      - 13.7. University of Pennsylvania, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, 13.8.
      - 1100.00. Miscellaneous Publications, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 45)
      - 13.8. Miscellaneous Publications, 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - 13.8. Miscellaneous Publications, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 2-4)
      - 13.8. Miscellaneous Publications, 1994-1995 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Published Remarks, 1100.01A.
      - 1100.01A. Miscellaneous Published Remarks, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Position Announcements, 13.9.
      - 1100.02. Position Announcements, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - 13.9. Position Announcements, 1995-1996 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Subject Files, 1991-1995; II.
  The files in Series II include those that could be considered subject files – those that do not fit into the mail log numbering but represent specific topics for O'Connor's research and work as chancellor. These include mostly meeting materials for the Chancellor's Executive Staff Meetings, but also some copies of remarks and agendas for semi-annual Board of Trustees meetings and information on the NCAA Infractions report prepared by the university.
  - General, 1.
    - Business Higher Education Forum European trip, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 1-2)
    - Conference proceedings, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, pre-Chancellorship, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Directory of Black Faculty (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Jaynes, Oval (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Maher, Jim (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - NCAA Infractions - Pitt report (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - NCAA Infractions - Exhibits for Governance and Compliance (Box 66, Folder 9-10)
    - NCAA Infractions - Pitt report, including exhibits (Box 66, Folder 11-12)
    - NCAA Infractions - Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 13-14)
    - Nordenberg, Mark (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Public Safety (Box 66, Folder 16-17)
    - Search Committees (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Search for the Senior Vice Chancellor for Business & Finance (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Staff Handbook (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Stark, William (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Tuchi, Ben (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 2.
    - Meeting notes and materials, June 24, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Meeting notes and materials, October 22, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Meeting notes and materials, February 17, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Meeting notes and materials, June 30, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Meeting notes and materials, October 21, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Meeting notes and materials, February 16, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Meeting notes and materials, June 22, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Senior Staff Meetings, 3.
    - Meeting dates, August 1991 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Meeting notes and materials, August 1991 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Meeting notes and materials, September 1991 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Meeting notes and materials, October 1991 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Meeting notes and materials, November 1991 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Meeting notes and materials, December 1991 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Meeting notes and materials, January 1992 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Meeting notes and materials, February 1992 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Meeting notes and materials, March 1992 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Meeting notes and materials, May 1992 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Meeting notes and materials, July 1992 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Meeting notes and materials, September 1992 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Meeting notes and materials, October 1992 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Meeting notes and materials, November 1992 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Meeting notes and materials, December 1992 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Meeting notes and materials, January 1993 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Meeting notes and materials, February 1993 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Meeting notes and materials, March 1993 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Meeting notes and materials, April 1993 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Meeting notes and materials, May 1993 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Meeting notes and materials, June 1993 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Meeting notes and materials, July 1993 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Meeting notes and materials, September 1993 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Meeting notes and materials, October 1993 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Meeting notes and materials, November 1993 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Meeting notes and materials, December 1993 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Executive Staff Meetings, 4.
    - Meeting notes and materials, March 1992 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Meeting notes and materials, April 1992 (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Meeting notes and materials, July 1992 (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Meeting notes and materials, September 1992 (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Meeting notes and materials, October 1992 (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Meeting notes and materials, November 1992 (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Meeting notes and materials, December 1992 (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - Meeting notes and materials, January 1993 (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Meeting notes and materials, February 1993 (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - Meeting notes and materials, March 1993 (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - Meeting notes and materials, April 1993 (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - Meeting notes and materials, June 1993 (Box 67, Folder 45)
    - Meeting notes and materials, July 1993 (Box 67, Folder 46)
    - Meeting notes and materials, September 1993 (Box 67, Folder 47)
    - Meeting notes and materials, October 1993 (Box 67, Folder 48)
    - Meeting notes and materials, November 1993 (Box 67, Folder 49)
    - Meeting notes and materials, December 1993 (Box 67, Folder 50)
    - Meeting notes and materials, January 1995 (Box 67, Folder 51)
    - Meeting notes and materials, February 1995 (Box 67, Folder 52)
    - Meeting notes and materials, March 1995 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Meeting notes and materials, April 1995 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Meeting notes and materials, May 1995 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Calendars, 5.
    - 1993 Calendar (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - 1994 Calendar (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - 1995 Calendar (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Chronological Files, 1991-1995; III.
  The chronological files for Chancellor O'Connor's administrative records are comprised of outgoing mail directly from O'Connor. They are sorted by date, reflecting the original organization from the Chancellor's Office. The records in this series may complement or duplicate material already found in the mail log records in Series I.
  - Chronological Files, 1991; 1.
    - Chronological Files, May 1991 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Chronological Files, June 1991 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Chronological Files, August 1991 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Chronological Files, September 1991 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Chronological Files, October 1991 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Chronological Files, November 1991 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Chronological Files, December 1991 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Chronological Files, 1992; 2.
    - Chronological Files, January 1992 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Chronological Files, February 1992 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Chronological Files, March 1992 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Chronological Files, April 1992 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Chronological Files, May 1992 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Chronological Files, June 1992 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Chronological Files, July 1992 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Chronological Files, August 1992 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Chronological Files, September 1992 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Chronological Files, October 1992 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Chronological Files, November 1992 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Chronological Files, December 1992 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Chronological Files, 1993; 3.
    - Chronological Files, January 1993 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Chronological Files, February 1993 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Chronological Files, March 1993 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Chronological Files, April 1993 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Chronological Files, May 1993 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Chronological Files, June 1993 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Chronological Files, October 1993 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Chronological Files, November 1993 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Chronological Files, December 1993 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Chronological Files, 1994; 4.
    - Chronological Files, January 1994 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Chronological Files, February 1994 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Chronological Files, March 1994 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Chronological Files, April 1994 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Chronological Files, May 1994 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Chronological Files, June 1994 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Chronological Files, July 1994 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Chronological Files, August 1994 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Chronological Files, September 1994 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Chronological Files, October 1994 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Chronological Files, November 1994 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Chronological Files, December 1994 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Chronological Files, 1995; 5.
    - Chronological Files, January 1995 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Chronological Files, February 1995 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Chronological Files, March 1995 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Chronological Files, April 1995 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Chronological Files, May 1995 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Chronological Files, June 1995 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Chronological Files, July 1995 (Box 69, Folder 26)
- Speeches, 1991-1995; IV.
  Series IV consists of the speeches given by O'Connor during his time as chancellor. They are sorted individually by date, retaining the original order in which they were organized by the Chancellor's Office. Files here generally consist of a transcript of O'Connor's remarks for a given event, though sometimes there are only brief notes or talking points for him to cover. Some events also include supplementary material, such as event programs or brief, related correspondence, but this is not the case for every event. Some items in this series are not actual speeches, but rather messages written as a greeting or commentary from the chancellor for publication. An index of speeches is available at the beginning of the series, though some speeches found in the series are not necessarily present in this index.
  - Speeches index (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Report to the Board of Trustees, September 12, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - United Way Cabinet meeting, September 20, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Economic Club of Pittsburgh, September 26, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Luncheon Lecture Series, September 30, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Remarks to Regional Campuses, September 1991 (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Minority Enterprise Development Week Awards luncheon, October 4, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Materials Research press conference, October 14, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Remarks to Faculty Senate on Governance, October 16, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Washington County Economic Development, October 18, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Rededication of new Salk Hall, October 18, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - Arts and Sciences Board of Visitors, October 27, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 38)
  - Law Fellows Breakfast, October 28, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Pennsylvania Congressional Delegation, October 30, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 40)
  - Boston Alumni event, November 1, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 41)
  - Black Scholarship Initiative reception, November 5, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 42)
  - Staff Association Council, November 5, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 43)
  - Katz Graduate School of Business Leadership reception, November 5, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 44)
  - "My First 100 Days", November 8, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 45)
  - Engineering Faculty Meeting, November 20, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 46)
  - Remarks for Trustees Meeting luncheon, November 22, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Materials Research presentation, November 22, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Leadership Seminar at Carnegie Mellon University, November 22, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Dickson Prize, November 25, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Student Government Induction, December 2, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - "New CEO in Town", December 4, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - School of Education Faculty Assembly, December 4, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Heinz Distinguished Lecture - Nelson Mandela, December 6, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Senate Council, December 9, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Welcome to New Employees, December 1991 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - 20-Year Staff Recognition Ceremony, December 17, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Robert Langer Introduction for Miles Lectureship, January 23, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Greater Pittsburgh Rotary Club luncheon, January 29, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Business-Education Forum, February 7, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Beth Shalom Congregation Men's Club Brotherhood Sabbath Services, February 8, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - "K-12 Speech", February 22, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Allegheny Country Club, February 23, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Remarks for Trustees Meeting, February 28, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - O'Connor Installation Address, February 28, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Background Statement for Laird election, February 1992 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - "Meet the Editors", February 1992 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - YMCA of Pittsburgh Annual Meeting, March 10, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - East Hills Pitt Club, March 18, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Honors Convocation script, March 19, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Medical Ethics talk, March 19, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Allegheny County Democratic delegation, March 20, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Remarks for Engineering Alumni, March 26, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Pittsburgh Cancer Institute retreat, March 27, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Chancellor's Band Concert, April 5, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Margaret Thatcher dinner, April 6, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Provost's Inaugural Lecture: Dr. Bartley Griffith, April 16, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Washington, D.C. Area Alumni event, April 21, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Chancellor's Report to Trustees, April 23, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - Dr. Vartan Gregorian Press Conference, April 26, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Commencement, April 26, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Planned Giving Council remarks, April 27, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Remarks to Cuba scholars, April 27, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Dedication of McGowan Center, May 6, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Notes for interview with international media, May 7, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Chicago Area Alumni event, May 8, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 40)
  - NCAA Press Conference, May 11, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 41)
  - Alumni Association meeting, May 12, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 42)
  - Southern California Alumni event (Box 70, Folder 43)
  - David M. Roderick Chair remarks, May 20, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 44)
  - Dental Medicine diploma ceremony, May 30, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 45)
  - Cell Transplant conference, June 1, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 46)
  - Greensburg Central Catholic graduation, June 3, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 47)
  - Pennsylvania Congressional delegation, June 3, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 48)
  - Executive MBA Alumni event, June 16, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 49)
  - 25th Anniversary of Hillman Library, June 18, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 50)
  - Chancellor's Report to Trustees, June 19, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 51)
  - Background Statement for Romoff election, June 1992 (Box 70, Folder 52)
  - Testimony before PA Senate Education Commission on Fiscal Accountability and Higher Education, June 1992 (Box 70, Folder 53)
  - Senate Council, July 13, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 54)
  - Helen Poole Rush Memorial Service, July 15, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 55)
  - Olympiad picnic, July 16, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 56)
  - United Way Kickoff, August 3, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 57)
  - Football Season Kickoff, August 31, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 58)
  - Sutherland Hall opening, September 2, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 59)
  - Lantern Night, September 2, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 60)
  - New Faculty Orientation, September 4, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 61)
  - Remarks for picnic supper, September 5, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 62)
  - Cultural Diversity celebration, September 16, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 63)
  - Male-mediated Developmental Toxicity conference, September 17, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 64)
  - Kosciuszko Foundation reception, September 18, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 65)
  - Senate Council, September 21, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 66)
  - Pittsburgh Blind Association, September 24, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 67)
  - Freshmen Parents Day, September 26, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 68)
  - Manufacturing Systems Engineering Program conference, September 29, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 69)
  - Pittsburgh High Technology Council, September 30, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 70)
  - Senior Vice Chancellor for Health Sciences charge, September 30, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 71)
  - Social Work PhD Remarks, October 1, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 72)
  - Katz Graduate School of Business Board of Visitors remarks, October 5, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 73)
  - Philadelphia Alumni Club event, October 16, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 74)
  - Remarks to Board of Trustees, October 23, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 75)
  - Communications Board of Visitors, October 23, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 76)
  - Remarks to the "Minute Men", October 28, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 77)
  - American Literary Translators Association Conference, October 30, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 78)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, November 10, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 79)
  - Wherrett Lecture series, November 16, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 80)
  - Golden Panther and Westinghouse Pitt-Penn State Luncheon, November 19, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 81)
  - Faculty of Arts & Sciences Board of Visitors, November 22-23, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 82)
  - Eagle Scout Recognition Dinner, November 24, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 83)
  - Dickson Prize, December 2, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 84)
  - The Chinese University of Hong Kong, December 7-9, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 85)
  - Senate Council, December 7, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 86)
  - Association of Governing Boards Advisory Council of Presidents, December 7, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 87)
  - Remarks to Board of Trustees Executive Committee, December 10, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 88)
  - 20-Year Staff Recognition Awards, December 15, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 89)
  - Pittsburgh Rotary Club Ethics Symposium, January 12, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 90)
  - Leadership Development Program for Freshman - "Emerging Leaders", January 13, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 91)
  - Academy of Students of Pharmacy, January 20, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 92)
  - Central Pennsylvania Pitt Club reception in Harrisburg, January 25, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 93)
  - Penn-Ohio Pitt Club reception, February 11, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 94)
  - Remarks to Board of Trustees, February 18, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 95)
  - Remarks to University Trust, February 18, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 96)
  - Honors Convocation, Founders Day, and State of the University address, February 26, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 97)
  - Alumni Association National Leaders conference, February 27, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 98)
  - "Bridging the World", February 1993 (Box 70, Folder 99)
  - Calvary Episcopal Church, March 1, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 100)
  - "Trade Fair" breakfast, March 9, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 101)
  - "Friends of Scouting" Montour District breakfast, March 16, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 102)
  - Concordia Club, March 25, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 103)
  - Phi Beta Kappa reception, March 30, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 104)
  - Remarks for University Challenge for Excellence Programs newsletter, March 1993 (Box 70, Folder 105)
  - Center for Biotechnology and Bioengineering, April 2, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 106)
  - Briefing Paper for Higher Education Secretariat, April 6, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 107)
  - Philadelphia Pitt Club reception, April 13, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 108)
  - Pitt Ambassadors Scholarship dinner - Dick Cheney, April 22, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 109)
  - Pitt Club of Chicago Goldberg Reception dinner, April 23, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 110)
  - Europe Business Opportunity Conference, April 26, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 111)
  - Distinguished Faculty Awards reception, April 27, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 112)
  - Blue and Gold Society induction, April 28, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 113)
  - Reception for Deans Bolvin, Nordenberg, and Sorber, April 29, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 114)
  - Commencement, May 1, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 115)
  - Young Presidents' Organization, May 7, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 116)
  - Japan/Korea/Hong Kong/Taiwan speeches, May 1993 (Box 70, Folder 117)
  - Senate Council, June 7, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 118)
  - Association of Governing Boards panel discussion, June 8, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 119)
  - "Vision for the Future of the University of Pittsburgh", June 8, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 120)
  - Detre Professorship dinner, June 9, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 121)
  - Robert M. Murphy Endowed Chair reception, June 10, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 122)
  - "The University of Pittsburgh: 1993 and Beyond", June 21, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 123)
  - Reception for Dr. Thomas Detre, June 22, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 124)
  - Remarks to the Board of Trustees, June 24, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 125)
  - Indian Nationality Room Declaration of Gift presentation, July 21, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 126)
  - International Herpesvirus conference, July 25, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 127)
  - Provost and Senior Vice Chancellor Search charge, July 28, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 128)
  - Chancellor's message for Alumni Annual Report, July 1993 (Box 70, Folder 129)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Clinical Scholars site visit, August 5, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 130)
  - Reception for African American and Hispanic freshmen and families, August 28, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 131)
  - Freshman Convocation, August 29, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 132)
  - Panthers Football kickoff, August 30, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 133)
  - Lantern Night, August 31, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 134)
  - New Faculty Orientation, September 3, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 135)
  - Unveiling of Jonas Salk portrait, September 9, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 136)
  - Berlin/Brandenburg Business Delegation, September 16, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 137)
  - American Association of Colleges of Nursing, September 17, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 138)
  - Cultural Diversity Celebration, September 21, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 139)
  - 5th Annual Scholars Program, September 24, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 140)
  - Remarks to Biomedical Graduate Students, September 24, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 141)
  - Chancellor's remarks for Alumni Annual Report, September 1993 (Box 70, Folder 142)
  - Pittsburgh - Konstanz Colloquium, October 1, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 143)
  - Remarks to Freshman parents, October 2, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 144)
  - Dedication of Forrest Continuing Education Center, October 15, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 145)
  - Savina Skewis Memorial, October 15, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 146)
  - Homecoming luncheon, October 15, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 147)
  - Alumni Association Board meeting, October 16, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 148)
  - Visiting Nurse Association, October 20, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 149)
  - University of Pittsburgh Trust Report of the President, October 22, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 150)
  - Chancellor's remarks to the Board of Trustees, October 22, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 151)